{
  "collection": {
    "name": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
    "description": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
    "hidden": "false"
  },
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "die",
      "back": "Kleidung oblečení",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Edelstein",
      "back": "skvost, klenot",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Handtasche",
      "back": "kabelka",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Hemd",
      "back": "košile",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Hut",
      "back": "klobouk",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Jacke",
      "back": "kabát, bunda",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Koffer",
      "back": "kufr",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Kragen",
      "back": "límec",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Krawatte",
      "back": "kravata, vázanka",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Mantel",
      "back": "kabát",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Ring",
      "back": "prsten",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Rock",
      "back": "sukně",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Schuh",
      "back": "střevíc, bota",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Socke",
      "back": "ponožka",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Stiefel",
      "back": "bota",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "Stoff",
      "back": "látka, tkanina",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Oblečení",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    }
  ],
  "settings": {
    "id": 1,
    "playVoiceText": "true",
    "languageOfVoice": "de",
    "typeOfVoice": "f2",
    "volumeOfVoice": 100,
    "displayAnswer": "false",
    "displayAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "limitTAnswer": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTime": 60,
    "showAnswerTime": "false",
    "limitTAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTimeByRepeating": 60,
    "showAnswerTimeByRepeating": "false",
    "filteringCards": "true"
  }
}
